what's up everyone tv5 here with a very
special video today
now I'm doing like my favorite my second
favorite thing and
and that is like watching my second
everything behind watching soccer up to
themselves
and that is like watching Sonic
Underground enemies now normally I watch
like Bobby exactly in these
which on my own because I'm 14-0 and
let me make sock ex Bobby's so right now
I'm just like watching a mavic
with a Hedgehog and I thought
i I'm gonna record this like go
but because why the now like this
amv it's it's called somewhat I belong
um
a tribute to like magic the Hedgehog and
and like the the the youtuber's name is
uh
i don't know
i don't give a you'll find it
somehow like
so yeah like if the videos come
somewhere belong contribute to mac the
Hedgehog and
so like how about we just get this
started shall we
here we go oh that was a cool beginning
the way to the soccer ball go oh
that was cool like it failed to
watch your Manic
hopefully you can hear my voice because
the music's up pretty loud but if you
can like
i don't give a back then you'll
just hear the ambient
[Music]
oh that was cool I love that
i love socks on the ground
oh did you see that why that was cool
that was like a spinning
that was badass I i love
that matcha hoverboard you don't got
that
in that modern Sonic like they
don't go like hoverboards like
Manic though I mean I think they might
but
it's not as cool if you know what I mean
go I'm just saying like you can't go
wrong with like rap
music like black people music and like
mad as a Hedgehog
oh that was cool
there was like a beatdrop oh
that
face I can't believe this
i can't believe it I didn't know that
feeling fate wasn't even with a moon
maker
like I didn't know that there's no
damn that was cool
it means mac looks so badass
that was cool
i love it I love all that like it's
spinning that transition
that was bitching I love that
oh that dabbing fade I mean that
that's just not even when of my making
so I guess it's not using sony vegas and
like
at that point I don't give a
anymore like
only don't use the winners on
that girl
like the way I see people clap that was
cool though
that was the timing thing that was
i love that I love that
that was cool like the music allowed and
i love it
why don't more people make psychology
did you just see that winking thing
again
i thought he used that winking animation
to be a
everyone knows that the first rule
making music you know what you seen
you just took me out of the experience
what's your name
i don't know I don't give a
you don't get the credit
i came out and you say your name you
ruined that
everybody knows there's a photo of
making that was a cool look oh that was
what the
the cool two traditions that was
i love that though that was the bitch
I'm gonna my pants oh my God
this video was coming 2010
i thought it was just I thought it was
new
what am I reacting to then
i mean I guess it made sense I'm not the
only soccer oh my God
the explosion was cool it was like
and there was like sparkles and a fire
and
that was that was bitching
is that it
that was the did you like stop in the
middle of the song
you you
you claim your luck man but you like
couldn't even
finish the amv
if you're not gonna face amv why did you
make it
am I the only one thinking this
how does this video got 8 000 views
my map my bulldog game means get like
what the
wait why am I even reacting here from
this is all that's fun if I wanna
what the I'm pissed
yeah that's 2010 october 6th wow
i mean I guess it makes sense I am like
the only fan left and but
damn I feel like I'm wasting my
time up in this
I'm out of here late I mean
this
this is all that's fun if I wanna